【The fate that cannot be liberated】
[해방될 수 없는 운명]
[Episode 11]
[11화]
Master.
주인.
Rong Yu, I want to tear you apart.
Rong Yu, 나는 당신을 찢어 버리고 싶습니다.
He Jiuling,
허 지울링,
come over.
이리와.
Master.
주인.
leave!
떠나다!
What happened to you last night?
어젯밤에 무슨 일이 있었나요?
I can accept your usual unruliness.
나는 당신의 평소 무례함을 받아들일 수 있습니다.
but why do you
그런데 너는 왜 그래?
Were you with him last night?
어젯밤에 그 사람이랑 같이 있었어?
If anyone else knows about this,
다른 사람이 이 사실을 알고 있다면,
How can I get married in the future?
앞으로 어떻게 결혼할 수 있나요?
I don't plan to get married.
나는 결혼할 계획이 없습니다.
A-And he doesn't understand anything. Don't imagine things.
A-그리고 그는 아무것도 이해하지 못합니다. 상상하지 마십시오.
why your room
왜 네 방이야?
A mess?
엉망?
That's because I couldn't sleep last night.
어젯밤에 잠을 못 잤기 때문이에요.
So I practiced some martial arts.
그래서 무술을 좀 연습했어요.
Back off.
물러나 다.
Stand further away.
더 멀리 서십시오.
Why are your lips swollen?
입술은 왜 부어있나요?
they are?
그들은?
All right.
괜찮은.
DD-Don't overthink it.
DD-너무 깊게 생각하지 마세요.
Look at your guilty expression.
죄책감을 느끼는 표정을 보세요.
You don't need to explain.
설명할 필요는 없습니다.
I totally get it.
나는 그것을 완전히 이해합니다.
Rong Yu!
유롱!
——He San! - you-
——그 산! - 너-
He San, you scared him.
그 산, 당신이 그 사람을 겁줬어요.
Get out of my sight.
내 눈 앞에서 사라져.
Go back to your own mansion.
자신의 저택으로 돌아가세요.
It was Astrology Day a few days ago and everyone was very busy.
며칠 전 점성술의 날이었고 모두가 매우 바빴습니다.
After seeing him perform well, we let our guard down.
그가 잘하는 모습을 보고 우리는 긴장을 풀었습니다.
Unexpectedly, he took the opportunity to leave Xingxiang Pavilion.
뜻밖에도 그는 Xingxiang Pavilion을 떠날 기회를 잡았습니다 .
If it weren't for your message, I'm afraid? ? ?
당신의 메시지가 아니었다면 유감인가요? ? ?
Forget it.
잊어 버려.
meet him
그를 만나다
Just a coincidence.
단지 우연의 일치입니다.
I don't know if this is a coincidence.
이것이 우연인지는 모르겠습니다.
Every time the young master gets lost,
젊은 주인이 길을 잃을 때마다,
It seems to be related to you.
당신과 관련이 있는 것 같습니다.
But it doesn't seem to have anything to do with you either.
하지만 그것도 당신과 아무 관련이 없는 것 같습니다 .
Has he ever been lost before?
그 사람이 전에 길을 잃은 적이 있나요?
He has gotten lost twice in recent years.
그는 최근 몇 년 동안 두 번이나 길을 잃었습니다.
The first time was three years ago.
처음은 3년 전이었습니다.
The young master wants to eat wontons on the street.
젊은 주인은 길거리에서 만두를 먹고 싶어한다.
Zhan Ping bought wontons.
잔핑은 완탕을 샀습니다.
And the young master disappeared in the blink of an eye.
그리고 젊은 스승은 눈 깜짝할 사이에 사라졌다.
Master,
주인,
I need a prescription to fill my prescription.
처방전을 조제하려면 처방전이 필요합니다.
I can't give you medicine without a prescription.
처방전 없이는 약을 줄 수 없습니다.
How about it
어때요?
Do you invite others over?
다른 사람을 초대하시나요?
Time is running out.
시간이 얼마 남지 않았습니다.
He Jiuling is sick. She needs medicine.
He Jiuling은 아프다. 그녀는 약이 필요해요.
Excellent? ? ? Master! Master!
훌륭한? ? ? 주인! 주인!
- Master! - Master.
- 주인! - 주인.
Master, why are you here?
선생님, 왜 여기 계시나요?
let's go. We go home.
갑시다. 우리는 집에 간다.
medicine!
약!
Master.
주인.
medicine! medicine!
약! 약!
Was it February three years ago?
3년 전 2월이었나?
how do you know?
어떻게 알아?
The other time was last winter.
다른 때는 지난 겨울이었다.
The young master ran further.
젊은 주인은 더 멀리 달렸습니다.
He said: "He Jiuling is cold."
그는 "그 Jiuling은 춥다"고 말했습니다.
Miss He?
미스 그?
It doesn't matter.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
I was just a little distracted.
나는 조금 산만했습니다.
The young master wants to find you.
젊은 주인이 당신을 찾고 싶어합니다.
But he doesn't know where you are.
하지만 그 사람은 당신이 어디에 있는지 모릅니다.
So he went to the cold
그래서 그는 추운 곳으로 갔어
And toward where there is water.
그리고 물이 있는 곳으로.
When we found him,
우리가 그를 찾았을 때,
His feet were frostbitten.
그의 발은 동상에 걸렸습니다.
Blood spurts from his boots
부츠에서 피가 뿜어져 나온다
Ice entered.
얼음이 들어갔습니다.
Miss He.
미스 헤.
why are you crying?
왜 울고 있어요?
I am very happy.
나는 매우 행복합니다.
I'm glad you're okay.
너가 괜찮다 니 다행이다.
I'm glad you can talk again.
다시 얘기할 수 있어서 기뻐요.
I'm glad we can meet again.
다시 만날 수 있어서 기뻐요.
I was so happy that I wanted to cry.
너무 기뻐서 울고 싶었습니다.
Then I wanted to cry too.
그러면 나도 울고 싶었어요.
No.
아니요.
No, you can't cry.
아니, 울면 안 돼요.
I like your smile.
난 너의 미소가 좋아.
In the days to come, you must always smile.
앞으로는 항상 웃어야 합니다.
I once had a plague.
나는 한때 전염병에 걸렸습니다.
The doctor said
의사가 말했다.
I only have one month left to live.
이제 살 날이 한 달밖에 남지 않았습니다.
But I have to survive.
하지만 나는 살아남아야 해요.
Not just for a month.
한 달만이 아닙니다.
Not just for one year.
단지 1년 동안이 아닙니다.
I have to live my life.
나는 내 삶을 살아야 한다.
otherwise,
그렇지 않으면,
no one can change you
누구도 너를 바꿀 수 없어
That smart and talented Rong Yu,
그 똑똑하고 재능있는 Rong Yu,
You will never be truly happy in your life.
당신은 인생에서 결코 진정으로 행복하지 않을 것입니다.
And that winter,
그리고 그해 겨울,
I was trapped by the Canglan River in a snowstorm,
나는 눈보라 속에서 창란강 에 갇혔고 ,
I'm cold and sleepy,
춥고 졸려요
A pack of hungry wolves stared at me.
배고픈 늑대 한 무리가 나를 쳐다보았다.
They are waiting for me to go to sleep.
그들은 내가 잠들기를 기다리고 있습니다.
But I couldn't let them catch me.
그러나 나는 그들이 나를 붙잡도록 놔둘 수 없었다.
I just shot a snow wolf and got its skin for you.
방금 눈늑대를 쏴서 가죽을 얻었습니다.
I haven't made you a cloak yet.
나는 아직 당신에게 망토를 만들지 않았습니다.
How can I sleep?
어떻게 잠을 잘 수 있나요?
But how do you know I'm sick?
그런데 내가 아픈 걸 어떻게 알죠?
How do you know I'm cold?
내가 추운 걸 어떻게 알죠?
Have you read the stars again?
별을 다시 읽어보셨나요?
What is Xingdu?
싱두(Xingdu)란 무엇인가?
I just know a lot of things.
나는 많은 것을 알고 있습니다.
You are the best
너는 최고야
in Jialin.
지알린에서.
future,
미래에
Can you stop worrying about me?
나에 대해 걱정하는 걸 그만둘 수 있나요?
I don't deserve it.
나는 그럴 자격이 없습니다.
what does that mean?
그게 무슨 뜻이야?
I mean, you should stop running around
내 말은, 뛰어다니는 걸 그만둬야 한다는 거야
And stop worrying people.
그리고 사람들을 걱정하지 마세요.
Eat whatever you want
먹고 싶은 것은 무엇이든 먹어라
And do what you love.
그리고 당신이 좋아하는 일을 하세요.
Don't care about others.
다른 사람에 대해 신경 쓰지 마십시오.
Just make sure you're happy.
당신이 행복한지 확인하세요.
I'm very happy now.
나는 지금 매우 행복합니다.
Then you and Heshan
그렇다면 당신과 허산
You should go home happily.
집에 행복하게 돌아가야 합니다.
Let's go home together.
같이 집에 가자.
You should go to your home.
당신은 당신의 집에 가야합니다.
I won't go with you.
나는 당신과 함께 가지 않을 것입니다.
Isn't it? ? ?
그렇지 않나요? ? ?
Won't you come together?
같이 가지 않을래?
I dont go.
나는 가지 않는다.
I still have unfinished business.
아직 끝나지 않은 일이 있어요.
Just go to Rongfu and wait for me?
그냥 Rongfu에 가서 나를 기다리나요?
Rong Yu,
유 롱,
You said you would listen to me
내 말을 들어준다고 했잖아
correct?
옳은?
I promise,
약속해요
I'll go to Rong Mansion to see you.
나는 당신을 만나러 롱 맨션에 갈 것입니다.
OK?
좋아요?
He Jiuling,
허 지울링,
Why are you crying as if we were separated forever?
왜 우리 가 영원히 헤어진 것처럼 울고 있나요 ?
How did you become so stupid?
어떻게 그렇게 바보가 되었나요?
After spending a day with Rong Yu?
Rong Yu와 하루를 보낸 후?
As a man, can't you be more straightforward?
남자로서 좀 더 솔직하게 말할 수는 없나요 ?
He Jiuling dislikes men
허지울링은 남자를 싫어한다
Those who are stubborn and indecisive.
고집이 세고 우유부단한 사람.
The more trouble you make, the less she likes you.
당신이 문제를 많이 일으킬수록 그녀는 당신을 덜 좋아합니다.
do you understand?
이해했나요?
is that so?
그렇습니까?
Okay, you'd better go back quickly.
알았어, 빨리 돌아가는 게 좋을 거야.
Don't let Mr. Rong
롱씨를 놔두지 마세요
blame him for running away
도망친 것에 대해 그를 비난하다
Got on Jiuling again.
다시 Jiuling에 도착했습니다.
do not Cry.
울지 마세요.
Rong Yu!
유롱!
- Rong Yu! - Jiuling!
- 롱 유! - 지우링!
Jiuling!
지울링!
Rong Yu!
유롱!
Don't listen to He San.
He San의 말을 듣지 마십시오.
What he said is wrong.
그가 말한 것은 틀렸다.
Even if others reject you
다른 사람들이 당신을 거부하더라도
I won't.
나는하지 않을 것이다.
No matter what you become,
당신이 무엇이 되든,
You will always be my best Rongyu.
당신은 항상 나의 최고의 Rongyu가 될 것입니다.
Indeed, every creature has its nemesis.
실제로 모든 생물에는 적이 있습니다.
I originally thought that for someone like He Jiuling,
원래는 He Jiuling 같은 사람은
No man can conquer her.
어떤 남자도 그녀를 정복할 수 없습니다.
I didn't expect it to be such a man.
그런 사람일 거라고는 예상하지 못했어요.
Chenzhou!
천저우!
Yan Zhao,
자오얀,
You have served me for many years.
당신은 수년 동안 나에게 봉사했습니다.
We have walked through life and death together.
우리는 삶과 죽음을 함께 걸어왔습니다.
We are like sworn brothers.
우리는 의형제와 같습니다.
I did not expect
나는 기대하지 않았다
you will draw your sword
너는 검을 뽑을 것이다
Against my family today.
오늘 내 가족을 반대합니다.
The evidence is conclusive that you have committed treason.
당신이 반역죄를 저질렀다는 증거가 결정적입니다 .
For the country and family,
나라와 가족을 위해
For personal reasons, I cannot let you go.
개인적인 사정으로 인해 당신을 보내드릴 수 없습니다.
I just follow orders.
나는 단지 명령을 따를 뿐입니다.
His Majesty ordered
폐하께서 명령하셨다
when you arrive in the capital
수도에 도착하면
You will be arrested.
당신은 체포됩니다.
I hope you
나는 당신을 바랍니다
It won't embarrass me.
그것은 나를 당황하게 하지 않을 것이다.
So His Majesty summoned us
그래서 폐하께서 우리를 부르셨습니다.
Come back to Beijing and catch us.
베이징으로 돌아와서 우리를 잡아주세요.
Chenzhou.
천저우.
enough!
충분한!
If His Majesty wants us to die
폐하께서 우리가 죽기를 바라신다면
We have no choice but to die.
우리는 죽는 것 외에는 선택의 여지가 없습니다.
Generally,
일반적으로,
Considering our friendship,
우리의 우정을 생각해보면,
Please don't embarrass the women in our family.
제발 우리 가족의 여성들을 당황하게 하지 마세요 .
Well, I promise you.
글쎄요, 약속해요.
We will not tie Ms. Li down.
우리는 리 씨를 묶지 않을 것입니다.
Your servants will also get a decent burial.
당신의 종들도 품위 있게 장사될 것입니다.
Jiuling!
지울링!
show!
보여주다!
Tan?
탠 껍질?
Don't go back to the capital.
수도로 돌아가지 마세요.
what happened?
무슨 일이에요?
The imperial court has no intention of rewarding your family.
황실에서는 당신의 가족에게 보상할 생각이 없습니다.
General He, Master Chenzhou, and Master Qingxing
허 장군, 천저우 스승, 칭싱 스승
All have been arrested.
모두 체포되었습니다.
If you go back with Master Qiuting
Qiuting 사부님과 함께 돌아간다면
You will also be arrested.
당신도 체포될 것이다.
What?
무엇?
what are you saying?
당신이 무슨 말을하는거야?
What happened to Qingxing?
Qingxing에게 무슨 일이 일어났나요?
【He is a mansion】
【그는 저택이다】
how?
어떻게?
The mansion is crowded with people
저택은 사람들로 붐빈다
Waiting for us to walk into a trap.
우리가 함정에 빠지기를 기다리고 있습니다.
If we enter the mansion unknowingly,
자신도 모르게 저택에 들어가면,
We will be arrested.
우리는 체포될 것이다.
What happened?
무슨 일이에요?
Why is our family accused of treason?
왜 우리 가족은 반역죄로 기소됩니까?
What should we do now?
우리는 지금 무엇을해야합니까?
This is a baseless accusation.
이것은 근거 없는 비난이다.
There must be a misunderstanding.
분명 오해가 있을 겁니다.
He San, don’t you know the people from the legal department?
허산 씨, 법무팀 사람들을 모르시나요 ?
Okay, let's go find Minister Zhang.
좋아, 장 장관을 찾으러 가자.
He is a teacher in Chenzhou.
그는 Chenzhou의 교사입니다.
I think he will help us.
내 생각엔 그가 우리를 도와줄 것 같아요.
Let's go now.
이제 가자.
time is life. let's go.
시간은 생명이다. 갑시다.
Yang Ying?
양잉?
It doesn't matter.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
I'm just worried about Qingxing.
나는 단지 Qingxing이 걱정됩니다.
Given his character,
그의 성격을 고려하면,
He will not surrender without a fight.
그는 싸우지 않고 항복하지 않을 것입니다.
I'm afraid
나는 두려워
He must be in pain.
그는 분명 고통스러울 것이다.
Sister-in-law, I'm sorry.
며느리님, 죄송합니다.
Since my father and I refuse to plead guilty
아버지와 나는 유죄 인정을 거부하기 때문에
No doctor will come.
의사가 안 올 거예요.
Whether you admit it or not,
인정하든 안 하든,
No matter what, we cannot escape death.
무슨 일이 있어도 우리는 죽음을 피할 수 없습니다.
Your brother will let me and the baby in my belly be with him
네 형이 나와 내 뱃속의 아기도 그와 함께 있게 하리라
On the road to Hades.
하데스로 가는 길.
Our family of three will not be alone.
우리 세 식구는 혼자가 아닐 거예요.
Our He family owes you.
우리 He 가족은 당신에게 빚을 지고 있습니다.
You don't owe me anything.
당신은 나에게 빚진 것이 없습니다.
Found the love of my life
내 인생의 사랑을 찾았어요
Dying with him brought me joy.
그와 함께 죽는 것은 나에게 기쁨을 가져다주었다.
This is a decision I made four years ago.
이것은 제가 4년 전에 내린 결정입니다.
As long as Qiuting, Jiuling,
Qiuting, Jiuling,
It was enough for Yang Ying to escape this disaster .
양잉이 이 재앙을 피하는 것만으로 도 충분했다 .
Qiuting.
큐팅.
Jiuling.
지울링.
and? ? ?
그리고? ? ?
Since I first saw you,
당신을 처음 본 이후로,
It’s been 276 days.
276일이 지났습니다.
If you spend that much time with your pet, you must be feeling something, right?
반려동물과 그렇게 많은 시간을 보내다 보면 뭔가 기분이 좋아지겠죠?
i don't expect you
나는 당신을 기대하지 않습니다
Like me as much as I like you.
내가 당신을 좋아하는 만큼 나를 좋아하세요.
I just hope
나는 단지 희망한다
You'll give up a little bit of what you love
당신은 당신이 사랑하는 것을 조금 포기하게 될 것입니다
For He Jiuling, for me.
He Jiuling을 위해, 나를 위해.
Yang Ying.
양잉.
Qingxing?
칭싱?
I know the He family is in trouble.
나는 He 가족이 곤경에 처해 있다는 것을 알고 있습니다.
I shouldn't be swayed by personal reasons at that time.
그럴 때 개인적인 사정으로 흔들리면 안 된다 .
My fault.
내 잘못.
I can't drag her into it.
나는 그녀를 그 안으로 끌어들일 수 없습니다.
Master, it's already late at night.
선생님, 벌써 밤이 늦었어요.
Let's go back to bed.
다시 잠자리에 들자.
Master.
주인.
how far
얼마나 멀리
Is it "the future"?
"미래"인가요?
Is tomorrow the “future”?
내일은 '미래'인가?
At.
에.
uncle.
삼촌.
At,
에,
Why aren't you asleep so late?
왜 이렇게 늦게 안 자?
I'm waiting for someone.
나는 누군가를 기다리고 있습니다.
she says
그녀는 말한다
She will come to me.
그녀는 나에게 올 것이다.
At,
에,
go to sleep.
자러 가세요.
She won't come.
그녀는 오지 않을 것이다.
You've said the same thing before.
이전에도 같은 말을 하셨습니다.
But I met her.
하지만 나는 그녀를 만났습니다.
But this time, it's true.
하지만 이번에는 사실이다.
over there!
저기!
Catch them!
그들을 잡아!
stop!
멈추다!
release!
풀어 주다!
go!
가다!
Jiuling!
지울링!
let's go!
갑시다!
Jiuling, hold on.
지울링, 잠깐만요.
stop!
멈추다!
After them!
그 후에!
Jiuling,
지울링,
hang on.
잠깐만요.
Jiuling.
지울링.
Searching over there they can't get very far.
저쪽을 찾아봐도 그리 멀지 않습니다.
Go back and look carefully again.
돌아가서 다시 주의 깊게 살펴보세요.
Yes.
예.
Yang Ying?
양잉?
I'm here. Come pick me up.
나는 여기 있다. 나 데리러 와줘.
I'm not afraid of you.
나는 당신을 두려워하지 않습니다.
Don't let her get away.
그녀가 도망가도록 두지 마세요.
Come if you dare.
감히 오세요.
stop!
멈추다!
Are you guys?
여러분은요?
Not full?
가득 차지 않았나요?
You can't even catch up with women.
여자를 따라잡을 수도 없습니다.
Quickly? ? ?
빠르게? ? ?
Write a letter to your senior brother? ? ?
선배에게 편지를 쓰나요? ? ?
Senior brother? ? ?
선배? ? ?
Jiuling!
지울링!
do not scare me.
겁주지 마.
I will definitely find a way.
나는 반드시 방법을 찾을 것이다.
I will definitely find a way
반드시 방법을 찾아낼 거야
To save our families.
우리 가족을 구하기 위해.
It's just you and me now.
이제 당신과 나뿐입니다.
Jiuling.
지울링.
Your bones are pretty strong.
당신의 뼈는 꽤 튼튼합니다.
Whether you admit it or not,
인정하든 안 하든,
You have been convicted.
당신은 유죄 판결을 받았습니다.
General He,
그 장군님,
Even if you don't think about yourself,
스스로 생각하지 않아도,
You should think about your family.
가족에 대해 생각해야합니다.
Can you bear to see me?
나를 보고 참을 수 있나요?
Are you going to torture and interrogate Jiuling like this?
이렇게 Jiuling을 고문하고 심문 하시겠습니까?
Speaking of which,
말하자면,
my family suffered a lot
우리 가족 많이 고생했어요
and suffered a lot of neglect
그리고 많은 무시를 당했다
these years
이 년
because of her.
그녀 때문에.
My nephew's career was ruined.
내 조카의 경력이 망가졌습니다.
But since then,
하지만 그 이후로,
His ability to torture people
사람을 고문하는 그의 능력
Even better than the Department of Justice.
법무부보다도 낫네요.
I handed He Jiuling over to him.
나는 He Jiuling을 그에게 넘겨주었습니다.
General He,
그 장군님,
What do you think about this?
이것에 대해 어떻게 생각하세요?
Have you found her?
그녀를 찾았나요?
It's just a matter of time.
시간 문제 일뿐입니다.
Lord Song!
송주님!
Mr. Song,
송 씨,
We caught Yang Ying.
양잉을 잡았습니다.
General He.
장군 그.
General He,
그 장군님,
I have good news for you.
좋은 소식이 있습니다.
He Jiuling had already escaped.
He Jiuling은 이미 탈출했습니다.
But we still got something today.
하지만 오늘도 우리는 뭔가를 얻었습니다.
Father!
아버지!
——Yang Ying. - I'm not a patient person.
——양잉. - 나는 인내심이 강한 사람이 아니다.
I don't want to wait too long.
너무 오래 기다리고 싶지 않아요.
I'd love to try some of the punishments I plan to give Jiuling
나는 Jiuling에게 줄 처벌 중 일부를 시도하고 싶습니다.
in her.
그녀 안에.
to try or not to try
시도할 것인가, 시도하지 않을 것인가
It's up to you, General He.
그것은 당신에게 달렸습니다, 장군님.
Do you plead guilty?
당신은 유죄를 인정합니까?
you hope to!
당신은 희망합니다!
If you want anything, come to me!
원하는 것이 있으면 나에게로 오세요!
I, Yang Ying, am not afraid of you.
나 양잉은 당신을 두려워하지 않습니다.
you!
너!
Yang Ying?
양잉?
You beast!
이 짐승!
- Yang Ying? - You villain!
- 양잉? - 이 악당!
Yang Ying! Yang Ying!
양잉! 양잉!
You beast!
이 짐승!
If you have any questions, come to me!
질문이 있으시면 저에게 오세요!
two? ? ?
둘? ? ?
I have divorced her.
나는 그녀와 이혼했습니다.
I already? ? ?
이미 나는? ? ?
[Divorce Letter] I have divorced her.
[이혼편지] 나는 그 사람과 이혼했습니다.
She is not from the He family.
그녀는 He 가족 출신이 아닙니다.
she is not.
그녀는 아니다.
- Yang Ying! - Qingxing???
- 양잉! - 칭싱???
Qingxing,
칭싱,
if you divorce me
당신이 나와 이혼한다면
You might as well kill me.
당신은 나를 죽이는 편이 나을 수도 있습니다.
Yang Ying???
양영???
I plead guilty.
나는 유죄를 인정합니다.
General He,
그 장군님,
What did you say?
뭐라고 하셨나요?
louder please.
더 크게 주세요.
I said
나는 말했다
I will plead guilty.
나는 유죄를 인정하겠습니다.
I, He Liang,
나 허량,
Used my daughter's name
딸 이름을 사용했어요
Communicate with Xunnan.
Xunnan과 대화하세요.
I, He Liang,
나 허량,
i am a sinner
나는 죄인이다
Who committed treason.
반역죄를 저지른 사람.
Let my family hurry up.
우리 가족이 서두르도록 하세요.
Master Qiuting,
마스터 치우팅,
Will you still ask for help?
그래도 도움을 요청할 건가요?
Take good care of her.
그녀를 잘 돌봐주세요.
Hello, Your Highness.
안녕하세요, 전하.
[Prince Yong’s Mansion] Everyone else is waiting for your orders outside.
[용왕저택] 밖에서 모두가 당신의 명령을 기다리고 있습니다.
Let's enter the palace.
궁전에 들어가 보자.
Your Highness!
전하!
I have to go to Jialin.
나는 Jialin에 가야 해요.
Your Highness?
전하?
We don't have time, Your Highness.
시간이 없습니다, 전하.
Now that the king is dead,
이제 왕이 죽었으니,
- It's time-- - But in Jialin? ? ?
- 이제 시간이... - 그런데 자린에서는요? ? ?
Your Highness, no matter what
전하, 무슨 일이 있어도
We should focus on the present moment.
우리는 현재 순간에 집중해야 한다.
Jiuling is in danger.
Jiuling이 위험에 빠졌습니다.
Your Highness!
전하!
You have kept a low profile for 20 years.
당신은 20년 동안 조용히 지내왔습니다.
Isn’t it just for this day?
오늘만 그런거 아냐?
Victory or defeat will be decided at this moment.
승패는 이 순간 결정될 것이다.
if you give up now
지금 포기한다면
It's not worth it.
그것은 가치가 없어.
Your Highness, please think again!
전하, 다시 생각해 보십시오!
Senior brother,
선배,
help me.
도와주세요.
Senior brother.
선배.
Father. Father.
아버지. 아버지.
No, father.
아뇨, 아버지.
Jiuling,
지울링,
sorry.
죄송합니다.
Head to the palace.
궁전으로 향하세요.
My father's subordinate,
아버지의 부하,
Colleagues from Chenzhou,
천저우(Chenzhou)의 동료들,
Dear military comrades in Qingxing,
친애하는 칭싱군 동지 여러분!
And my good friends? ? ?
그리고 내 좋은 친구들은요? ? ?
I've reached out to everyone.
나는 모든 사람에게 연락했습니다.
No one wants to help us.
아무도 우리를 돕고 싶어하지 않습니다.
Master Qiuting,
마스터 치우팅,
At dusk today,
오늘 황혼 무렵,
General He and others will be taken to the cell at Liudaokou.
그 장군과 다른 사람들은 육도구의 감방 으로 끌려갈 것입니다 .
They will be executed within three days.
그들은 3일 안에 처형될 것이다.
From today,
오늘부터,
The Department of Justice will search every home looking for suspects.
법무부는 용의자를 찾기 위해 모든 가정을 수색할 것입니다.
[Wanted, Notified] Neighbors or hiders will also be punished.
[수배, 신고] 이웃이나 숨는 사람도 처벌됩니다.
Are there any neighbors? Under what law?
이웃이 있나요? 어떤 법에 따라?
Be careful
조심하세요
To avoid being implicated without knowing it.
자신도 모르게 연루되는 것을 방지하기 위함입니다.
We have to be very careful.
우리는 매우 조심해야 합니다.
now,
지금,
It's better for everyone to be careful.
다들 조심하시는 게 좋을 것 같아요.
[Ministry of Justice]
[법무부]
They are trying to catch General He's daughter.
그들은 장군의 딸을 잡으려고 합니다.
- move! - and their youngest son.
- 이동하다! - 그리고 막내아들.
Yes.
예.
They are trying to capture General He's daughter and son.
그들은 허 장군의 딸과 아들을 붙잡으려고 합니다.
What are their names?
그들의 이름은 무엇입니까?
Here they come.
여기 그들이 온다.
let's see.
보자.
It seems they have been tortured.
그들은 고문을 당한 것 같습니다.
The criminal He Liang,
범죄자 허량,
He Chenzhou,
허 천저우(He Chenzhou),
He Qingxing,
허칭싱,
Li, Yang
리양
Convicted of treason.
반역죄로 유죄 판결을 받았습니다.
The entire family will be executed.
온 가족이 처형될 것이다.
This is too tragic.
이것은 너무 비극적이다.
The execution will take place three days later at Liudaokou.
처형은 3일 뒤 류다오커우에서 이뤄질 예정이다.
The criminal He Liang,
범죄자 허량,
He Chenzhou,
허 천저우(He Chenzhou),
He Qingxing,
허칭싱,
Li, Yang
리양
Convicted of treason.
반역죄로 유죄 판결을 받았습니다.
The entire family will be executed.
온 가족이 처형될 것이다.
The execution will take place three days later at Liudaokou.
처형은 3일 뒤 류다오커우에서 이뤄질 예정이다.
The criminal He Liang,
범죄자 허량,
- He Chenzhou, - Get out!
- He Chenzhou, - 나가!
He Qingxing--
허칭싱--
Get lost now!
지금 길을 잃다!
How dare you tell me to get lost!
감히 나한테 길을 잃으라고 말하는 거야!
You will die soon. Let this be a lesson to you.
당신은 곧 죽을 것이다. 이것이 당신에게 교훈이 되도록 하십시오.
Father!
아버지!
- Father!
- 아버지!
Yes, I will die soon.
응, 난 곧 죽을 거야.
That's why I'm telling you to get lost.
그렇기 때문에 길을 잃으라고 말하는 것입니다.
Stay as far away as possible.
가능한 한 멀리 떨어져 있으십시오.
leave!
떠나다!
How defiant you are!
당신은 얼마나 반항적입니까!
move!
이동하다!
get lost.
길을 잃다.
Get lost quickly.
빨리 길을 잃으세요.
move!
이동하다!
As far away from me as possible.
나에게서 최대한 멀리.
Get lost quickly.
빨리 길을 잃으세요.
Move quickly.
빠르게 움직이다.
Get lost now!
지금 길을 잃다!
Jiuling and I are leaving.
Jiuling과 나는 떠난다.
where are you going?
어디 가세요?
She was not covered.
그녀는 보호되지 않았습니다.
Her fever had just gone down.
그녀의 열은 방금 떨어졌습니다.
I don't know either.
나도 모른다.
But if we stay here, we will implicate you.
하지만 우리가 여기에 머무르면 당신을 연루시킬 것입니다.
I'm not afraid.
나는 두렵지 않다.
I am.
그래요.
- But-- - Say no more.
- 하지만... - 더 이상 말하지 마세요.
Don’t embarrass Jiuling either.
Jiuling도 당황하게 하지 마세요.
You have done a lot for us.
당신은 우리를 위해 많은 일을 해왔습니다.
Jiuling.
지울링.
He San,
허 산,
when i fall asleep,
내가 잠들 때,
I heard people cursing my father.
사람들이 아버지를 저주하는 소리를 들었습니다.
They say my father is a criminal
우리 아버지가 범인이라고 하던데
traitor.
배신자.
That was a dream.
그것은 꿈이었습니다.
I have a clear mind. This is not a dream.
나는 명확한 마음을 가지고 있습니다. 이것은 꿈이 아닙니다.
nobody
아무도
Are you willing to help our family?
우리 가족을 기꺼이 도와주시겠어요?
We have nowhere to go,
우리는 갈 곳이 없습니다.
correct?
옳은?
My fault. I'm so useless
내 잘못. 난 너무 쓸모없어
gentlemen! gentlemen!
신사! 신사!
It's here.
여기 있어요.
There is a suspicious person here.
여기 수상한 사람이 있습니다.
- This way. - It's here.
- 이 방법. - 여기 있어요.
hurry up. Quickly.
서둘러요. 빠르게.
This is the place.
이곳이 바로 이곳이다.
right here.
바로 여기에.
hurry.
서두르다.
???Under the sunset at dusk? ? ?
???해질녘 노을 아래서요? ? ?
???I traveled thousands of miles to a distant place? ? ?
???나는 먼 곳으로 수천 마일을 여행했다고요? ? ?
???Playing the piano under the moonlight? ? ?
???달빛아래 피아노 연주? ? ?
???These drinks won’t make me forget? ? ?
???이 음료수는 잊혀지지 않을까요? ? ?
???The desire I wrote for you? ? ?
???내가 당신을 위해 쓴 소망은요? ? ?
??? Our destiny is written on paper? ? ?
??? 우리의 운명은 종이에 적혀있다고? ? ?
??? Like the strongest wine? ? ?
??? 최강의 와인을 좋아하시나요? ? ?
??? There is no way to escape fate? ? ?
??? 운명을 피할 방법은 없나요? ? ?
???Looking back, I saw you waiting? ? ?
???뒤돌아보니 기다리고 있는거 보이시죠? ? ?
???Our life is full of joy and sorrow? ? ?
???우리의 삶은 기쁨과 슬픔으로 가득 차 있습니까? ? ?
??? Desire to crystallize into a bright galaxy???
??? 밝은 은하계로 결정화되기를 원하시나요 ???
???You quietly turned around and closed the marriage certificate? ? ?
??? 조용히 돌아서서 결혼증명서를 닫았나요? ? ?
???Ask how many stars are there in the sky? ? ?
???하늘에 별이 몇 개 있는지 물어보세요. ? ?
???The desire I wrote for you? ? ?
???내가 당신을 위해 쓴 소망은요? ? ?
??? Our destiny is written on paper? ? ?
??? 우리의 운명은 종이에 적혀있다고? ? ?
??? Like the strongest wine? ? ?
??? 최강의 와인을 좋아하시나요? ? ?
??? There is no way to escape fate? ? ?
??? 운명을 피할 방법은 없나요? ? ?
???Looking back, I saw you waiting? ? ?
???뒤돌아보니 기다리고 있는거 보이시죠? ? ?
???Our life is full of joy and sorrow? ? ?
???우리의 삶은 기쁨과 슬픔으로 가득 차 있습니까? ? ?
??? Desire to crystallize into a bright galaxy???
??? 밝은 은하계로 결정화되기를 원하시나요 ???
???I gently caress the guzheng, waiting for passers-by like you???
???나는 고젱을 부드럽게 어루만지며 당신같은 행인을 기다린다???
???So you are my indissoluble bond? ? ?
???그럼 당신은 나의 불용성 유대인가요? ? ?